{
    "subject": "resource/Joey_Molland",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/The_Merseybeats",
    "human_readable": "Joey Molland was associated with The Merseybeats.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9699184894561768,
            "question": "Was Joey Molland in a band called The Merseybeats?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9632623791694641,
            "question": "When did Joey Molland perform with The Merseybeats?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8841524124145508,
            "question": "Who was associated with The Merseybeats?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6565191745758057,
            "question": "What other bands was Joey Molland involved with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5845351815223694,
            "question": "Where was The Merseybeats based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5036600828170776,
            "question": "What is The Merseybeats known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44121426343917847,
            "question": "Name the band that Joey Molland performed with."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3699183762073517,
            "question": "What music group was Joey Molland a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36052021384239197,
            "question": "What genre of music did The Merseybeats play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21500247716903687,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Joey Molland's musical career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joey Molland was associated with The Merseybeats.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8542_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music did The Merseybeats play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8542_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What music group was Joey Molland a part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8542_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the band that Joey Molland performed with.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8542_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8542_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8542_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8542_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8542_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8542_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8542_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8542_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8542_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8542_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8542_51.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents mention that Joey Molland played with a band called The Merseys, but there's no information about him being associated with The Merseybeats.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that the statement is supported by the documents. Here's the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that Joey Molland was associated with The Merseys (Billy Kinsley & Tony Crane from the now disbanded Merseybeats), as mentioned in document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8542/re-ranker-msmarco/40.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"In 1966, 3 members of The Masterminds, which included Joey, would be recruited to form a backing band for The Merseys (Billy Kinsley & Tony Crane from the now disbanded Merseybeats.).\" This indicates Joey Molland was associated with The Merseybeats at some point in his career."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Text 5 states that Billy Kinsley & Tony Crane from the now disbanded Merseybeats joined with 3 members of The Masterminds to form a backing band for The Merseys,  not that Joey Molland was associated with The Merseybeats.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}